http://fiberarts.org/privacy.php5

Privacy Policy
We respect your privacy.
No personal information is collected by Fiberarts.org from visitors to the website, when viewing pages. Email addresses of people who email us directly are also not collected or harvested, they are used only to respond to direct queries.
Our privacy policy is simple. We will never sell, rent, or share any information about you when you visit our web site or contact us. Steps have been taken to prevent email contact addresses on the site from the automatic collection by robots or other mechanical means, however, you should be aware that when you voluntarily disclose personal information (e.g., your name or email address) in discussion forums on this website, that information can be collected and used by others and may result in unsolicited messages from other posters or parties. Personal information collected will not be disclosed to any third party, except with the express approval of the individual, for example, when it appears in the Classified Ads. However, in no event shall Fiberarts.org be liable for the use or disclosure of such information.
Fiberarts.org reserves the right to remove any publicly posted content that it deems to be objectionable. This web site contains links to other web sites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are moving to another web site. You are encouraged to read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their privacy policy may differ from Fiberarts.org.
News
Search
Help
Privacy
Terms of Use
Contact Us
